### Your basket is empty

Have an account?

[Log in](https://puresportcbd.com/en-us/account/login) to check out faster.

Loading...

Order special instructions Order special instructions

Subtotal (TAX INCL.)

$0.00

Update

Check out

 Search 

* Shop
    
    * Enhance performance, improve endurance and reduce pain.

    * Apparel to propel you forward.

    [
    
    FOR THE LONG RUN
    
    Collection now live.
    
    SHOP. NOW](https://puresportcbd.com/en-us/collections/for-the-long-run)
    
* Our story

    [
    
    ATHLETES
    
    We believe in the power of our people.](https://puresportcbd.com/en-us/blogs/ambassadors)
    
    [
    
    OUR MISSION
    
    Join us For the Long Run.](https://puresportcbd.com/en-us/pages/our-mission)
    
* Community

    [
    
    COMMUNITY
    
    Be part of the community.](https://puresportcbd.com/en-us/pages/community)
    
    [
    
    EVENTS
    
    Join us at an Event.](https://puresportcbd.com/en-us/pages/events_calendar)
    
* The Hub

    [
    
    THE RUN DOWN
    
    Your regular update on all things Puresport.](https://puresportcbd.com/en-us/blogs/the-run-down)
    
    [
    
    PROJECT PURESPORT
    
    An unfiltered insight into the brand, people and community.](https://puresportcbd.com/en-us/blogs/puresport-project)

        Enhance performance, improve endurance and reduce pain.

        Apparel to propel you forward.

    [
    
    FOR THE LONG RUN
    
    Collection now live.
    
    SHOP. NOW](https://puresportcbd.com/en-us/collections/for-the-long-run)

    [
    
    ATHLETES
    
    We believe in the power of our people.](https://puresportcbd.com/en-us/blogs/ambassadors)
    
    [
    
    OUR MISSION
    
    Join us For the Long Run.](https://puresportcbd.com/en-us/pages/our-mission)

    [
    
    COMMUNITY
    
    Be part of the community.](https://puresportcbd.com/en-us/pages/community)
    
    [
    
    EVENTS
    
    Join us at an Event.](https://puresportcbd.com/en-us/pages/events_calendar)

    [
    
    THE RUN DOWN
    
    Your regular update on all things Puresport.](https://puresportcbd.com/en-us/blogs/the-run-down)
    
    [
    
    PROJECT PURESPORT
    
    An unfiltered insight into the brand, people and community.](https://puresportcbd.com/en-us/blogs/puresport-project)

[

FOR THE LONG RUN

Collection now live.

SHOP. NOW](https://puresportcbd.com/en-us/collections/for-the-long-run)

PRIVACY POLICY
==============

Puresport is committed to respecting and protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy sets out the basis on which any personal data we collect from you, or that you provide to us, will be processed by us. Please read the following carefully to understand our views and practices regarding your personal data and how will you will treat it.

For the purpose of the Data Protection Act 1998 (the Act), the data controller is Pure Sport Oil Ltd.

**Information we may collect from you**

* Information that you provide by filling in forms on our site www.puresport.co. This includes information provided at the time of registering to use our site, subscribing to our service, posting material or requesting further services. We may also ask you for information when you report a problem with our site.
* If you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence.
* Details of transactions you carry out through our site and of the fulfilment of your orders.
* Details of your visits to our site including, but not limited to, traffic data, location data, weblogs and other communication data, whether this is required for our own billing purposes or otherwise and the resources that you access.

​​Other advertising

We believe that advertising is more interesting to you when it is relevant. We may customise the advertising that you see based upon your personal information.

We may use personal information for this purpose including:

* the Information you voluntarily provide to us;
* geographic location information, which we may determine through your IP address, from your mobile device, or other ways;
* data we receive from third parties; or
* your visits to our website or your use of our services (commonly referred to as “Behavioural Advertising”) via the use of cookies.

You can control how cookies are used via your browser.

### IP addresses

We may collect information about your computer, including where available your IP address, operating system and browser type, for system administration and to report aggregate information to our advertisers. This is statistical data about our users’ browsing actions and patterns, and does not identify any individual.

### Cookies and our cookies policy

This section explains how and why we use cookies. Cookies are small text files placed on your device when you visit a website. We use cookies to recognise you and your preferences, enhance the performance of our website and collect analytical information.

Our website uses cookies to distinguish you from other users of our website. This helps us to provide you with a good experience when you browse our website and also allows us to improve our site.

It is our policy not to use “behavioural targeting” cookies as defined by the ICC Classifications. The cookies that we use fall within the strictly necessary, functionality and performance classifications.

This website uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. (“Google”) Google Analytics uses “cookies” to help the website analyse how users use the site. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website (including your IP address) will be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States. Google will use this information for the purpose of evaluating your use of the website, compiling reports on website activity for website operators and providing other services relating to website activity and internet usage. Google may also transfer this information to third parties where required to do so by law, or where such third parties process the information on Google’s behalf. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google. You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser, however please note that if you do this you may not be able to use the full functionality of this website. By using this website, you consent to the processing of data about you by Google in the manner and for the purposes set out above.

For the avoidance of doubt, if at any time you wish to disable our cookies you may do so through the settings on your browser, but if you do so you will not be able to use certain important features of our service.

### Where we store your personal data

The data that we collect from you may be transferred to, and stored at, a destination outside the European Economic Area (“EEA”). It may also be processed by staff operating outside the EEA who work for us or for one of our suppliers. Such staff may be engaged in, among other things, the fulfilment of your order, the processing of your payment details and the provision of support services. By submitting your personal data, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this privacy policy.

Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password which enables you to access certain parts of this website you must keep this password confidential and secure.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our site; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access.

### Uses made of the information

We use information held about you in the following ways:

* To ensure that content from our site is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer.
* To provide you with information, products or services that you request from us or which we feel may interest you, where you have consented to be contacted for such purposes.
* To carry out our obligations arising from any contracts entered into between you and us.
* To allow you to participate in interactive features of our service, when you choose to do so.
* To notify you about changes to our service.

We may also use your data to provide you with information about services which may be of interest to you and we may contact you about these by post or telephone.

### Disclosure of your information

We may disclose your personal information to any member of our group, which means our subsidiaries, our ultimate holding company and its subsidiaries, as defined in section 1159 of the UK Companies Act 2006.

We may disclose your personal information to third parties:

* In the event that we sell or buy any business or assets, in which case we may disclose your personal data to the prospective seller or buyer of such business or assets.
* If Puresport or substantially all of its assets are acquired by a third party, in which case personal data held by it about its customers will be one of the transferred assets.
* If we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply our terms of use and other agreements; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of Pure Sport Oil Limited, our customers, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organisations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

### Your rights

You have the right to ask us not to process your personal data for marketing purposes. We will inform you (before collecting your data) if we intend to use your data for such purposes or if we intend to disclose your information to any third party for such purposes. You can exercise your right to prevent such processing by checking certain boxes on the forms we use to collect your data. You can also exercise the right at any time by contacting us at contact@puresport.co.

Our site may, from time to time, contain links to and from the websites of our partner networks, advertisers and affiliates. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies. Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites.

### Changes to our privacy policy

Any changes we may make to our privacy policy in the future will be posted on this page and, where appropriate, notified to you by email.

### Contact

Questions, comments and requests regarding this cookies and privacy policy are welcomed and should be addressed to contact@puresport.co.

### Klarna

In order to be able to offer you Klarna’s payment options, we will pass to Klarna certain aspects of your personal information, such as contact and order details, in order for Klarna to assess whether you qualify for their payment options and to tailor the payment options for you.

General information on [Klarna](https://www.klarna.com/uk/) you can find here. Your personal data is handled in accordance with applicable data protection law and in accordance with the information in [Klarna’s privacy policy](http://cdn.klarna.com/1.0/shared/content/legal/terms/Klarna/en_gb/privacy).

### Rakuten Advertising

Rakuten Advertising may collect personal information when you interact with our digital property, including IP addresses, digital identifiers, information about your web browsing and app usage and how you interact with our properties and ads for a variety of purposes, such as personalization of offers or advertisements, analytics about how you engage with websites or ads and other commercial purposes. For more information about the collection, use and sale of your personal data and your rights, please use the below links:

Further information on Rakuten's Privacy Policy can be found [here](https://rakutenadvertising.com/legal-notices/services-privacy-policy/).

Your rights can be found [here](https://rakutenadvertising.com/legal-notices/services-privacy-rights-request-form/).

To opt out please click [here.](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/)

© 2024 Puresport. All of our products are sold as food supplements and not intended to diagnose, cure, prevent or treat disease. Always consult your health professional before taking any food supplements.

Payment methods

* American Express
* Apple Pay
* Diners Club
* Discover
* Google Pay
* Maestro
* Mastercard
* Shop Pay
* Union Pay
* Visa

* Choosing a selection results in a full page refresh.
* Opens in a new window.

Notify me when this product is in stock

  Enter your email Submit

You're in! We'll let you know when it's back.

 Sign-up to newsletter
